A Finding Aid to the Reginald Marsh Papers, 1897-1955, in the Archives of American Art AAA.marsregi
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, circa 1897-1908, 1920-1952; Series 8; (boxes 6-8, 10; 1.3 linear feet)
  - Artist, undated; 8.2
    - Oversize, Photographs of Marsh Sketching (taken by Gene Pyle), undated; (See Box 6, F39) (Box 10 (sol))
  - Art Work, 1920s-1952; 8.3
    Subseries consists of photographs of Marsh's art work, both loose and in disbound photograph albums. Volume 3 of the albums solely contains photographs of the murals he did for the New York Customs House and the Post Office Department, Washington, D.C. Album pages, which were removed from their 3-ring binders at some previous time, are often annotated with information about a particular art work, including title, date, and notes on the owner or disposition of a work. Loose photographs, also presumably compiled by Marsh, are organized according to particular project or exhibition. Many, if not all, of the miscellaneous photographs were compiled and/or reproduced by Norman Sasowsky for use in his catalog of Marsh's art work. Many of these are duplicates of those found in the albums.
    - Albums, 8.3.1
      - Volume 1, 1929-1933; (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
      - Volume 2, 1934-1938; (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 6-10)
      - Volume 3 (Custom House and Post Office Murals), circa 1935-1937; (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 11-15)
      - Volume 4, 1938-1940; (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 16-20)
      - Volume 5, 1940-1944; (5 folders) (Box 7, Folder 21-25)
      - Volume 6, 1944-1946; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 26-28)
      - Volume 7, 1947-1952; (4 folders) (Box 7, Folder 29-32)
    - Loose Photographs, 8.3.2
      - Paramount Theater Sets and Costumes, circa 1920s (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Carnegie Institute Exhibitions, 1931-1950 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Watercolors of U.S. Army Air Corps, Wright Field, Dayton, Ohio, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Custom House Murals (color transparencies), circa 1937; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 8.3.3
      - Early Art Work, 1920s; (Not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Marsh and Rehn Galleries Photographs of Various Works of Art, 1930s-1950s; (6 folders; see also Box 10; not scanned) (Box 7, Folder 38-43)
      - Various Works of Art, undated; (5 folders; not scanned) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 1-5)
      - Works by Other Artists (Sasowsky essays), undated; (Not scanned) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 6)
      - Works by Other Artists, undated; (Not scanned) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 7)
      - Oversize, Marsh and Rehn Galleries Photographs of Various Works of Art, 1930s-1950s; (Not scanned) (Box 10 (sol))
- Printed Material, 1931-1955; Series 9; (boxes 8, 10; 0.2 linear feet)
  Series consists of exhibition catalogs for Marsh's solo and groups shows (particularly ones at the Rehn Galleries) and a limited amount of clippings. Also included are several copies of Tow Line magazines and some related photographs of tugboats, which Marsh may have collected for their illustrations, a program, list of nominations, and blank proposal form related to the award Marsh received from the National Institute of Arts and Letters. Printed material is arranged in rough chronological order.
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1931-1953 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1944-1955, undated; (See also Box 10; not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Tow Line Magazines and Photographs, 1949-1953; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950-1953; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Printed Material Related to National Institute of Arts and Letters Award, 1954; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Oversize, Clippings, 1944-1955, undated; (Not scanned) (Box 10 (sol))